Hi, I'm Stan DeFreitas, Mr. Green Thumb for On Gardening.
Now this is a petunia variety called Wave.
And you can see the reason it's called Wave because it tends to just lap over every area.
Now there's a bunch of different kinds of petunias, which we've talked about in the past in different things, but the Wave Petunia is one that you'll find great for a hanging basket, or as a bedding plant where you want it to spill over into another area.
The Wave Petunias will flower just about every day, and they'll give you a bunch of flowers from early Spring through Fall, depending on where you're at.
Now petunias are fairly heavy feeders, so I'd make sure that you give it about every week or two about half strength with a good water soluble plant food.
You might also when you plant them, make sure it's got good peat and pearl like combination.
Many of the good mixes that are professional mixes will be good for this particular plant.
Remember in baskets, they tend to dry out a little bit quicker, so if you've got a hanging basket like this one is, you're going to have to make sure that you water it on almost a daily basis.
For On Gardening, I'm Stan DeFreitas, Mr. Green Thumb.